<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="63">
	<author>Bobster82</author>
	<title>
		<en>AutoRepair</en>
		<de>AutoRepair</de>
		<fr>AutoRepair</fr>
		<nl>AutoRepair</nl>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
		<![CDATA[ AutoRepair keeps your vehicle healty.

		+ Repairs your vehicle automaticly when it has damage.
		+ Repaint your vehicle automaticly when it has worn out.
		+ Clean your vehicle automaticly when it got dirty.

		## How to use:
		* When you place this mod in your fs22 mods folder, only auto repair is on by default.
		* Press Left Alt + r key to acces the menu.
				* Change the time interval when vehicles/tools needs to be checked.
				* Activate/deactivate auto repair.
				* Change at what damage percent a vehicle/tool get repaired.
				* Activate/deactivate auto repaint.
				* Change at what wear percent a vehicle/tool get repainted.
				* Activate/deactivate auto clean.
				* Change at what dirt percent a vehicle get cleaned.

		## Multiplayer:
		* You need admin rights to acces the settings menu
		* You can use global settings for all farms or change by farm

		This mod is made by me from scratch.

		If you have any issues with the mod or anything related, please contact me on:
		https://github.com/Bobster82/FS22_AutoRepair ]]>
		</en>

		<de>
		<![CDATA[ AutoRepair hält Ihr Fahrzeug gesund.

		+ Repariert Ihr Fahrzeug automatisch, wenn es beschädigt ist.
		+ Lackiert Ihr Fahrzeug automatisch neu, wenn es abgenutzt ist.
		+ Reinigt Ihr Fahrzeug automatisch, wenn es schmutzig geworden ist.

		## Wie zu verwenden:
		* Wenn Sie diese Mod in Ihrem fs22 Mods-Ordner platzieren, ist nur die automatische Reparatur standardmäßig aktiviert.
		* Drücken Sie die linke Alt + r Taste, um das Menü aufzurufen.
				* Ändern Sie das Zeitintervall, in dem Fahrzeuge/Werkzeuge überprüft werden müssen.
				* Aktivieren/Deaktivieren der Autoreparatur.
				* Ändern Sie den Prozentsatz des Schadens, den ein Fahrzeug/Werkzeug repariert wird.
				* Aktivieren/Deaktivieren der automatischen Neulackierung.
				* Ändert, ab welchem Verschleißprozentsatz ein Fahrzeug/Werkzeug neu lackiert wird.
				* Aktivieren/Deaktivieren der automatischen Reinigung.
				* Ändert, ab welchem Verschmutzungsgrad ein Fahrzeug gereinigt wird.

		## Multiplayer:
		* Sie benötigen Admin-Rechte, um auf das Einstellungsmenü zuzugreifen.
		* Du kannst globale Einstellungen für alle Farmen verwenden oder sie pro Farm ändern.

		Diese Mod wurde von mir von Grund auf neu erstellt.

		Wenn Sie irgendwelche Probleme mit der Mod oder irgendetwas damit zu tun haben, kontaktieren Sie mich bitte auf:
		https://github.com/Bobster82/FS22_AutoRepair ]]>
		</de>

		<fr>
		<![CDATA[ AutoRepair maintient votre véhicule en bonne santé.

		+ Répare automatiquement votre véhicule lorsqu'il est endommagé.
		+ Repeint automatiquement votre véhicule lorsqu'il est usé.
		+ Nettoie automatiquement votre véhicule lorsqu'il est sale.

		## Comment utiliser :
		* Lorsque vous placez ce mod dans votre dossier mods fs22, seule la réparation automatique est activée par défaut.
		* Appuyez sur la touche Alt gauche + r pour accéder au menu.
				* Changez l'intervalle de temps où les véhicules/outils doivent être vérifiés.
				* Activer/désactiver la réparation automatique.
				* Modifiez le pourcentage de dommages d'un véhicule/outil qui doit être réparé.
				* Activer/désactiver la peinture automatique.
				* Modification du pourcentage d'usure d'un véhicule/outil qui sera repeint.
				* Activez/désactivez le nettoyage automatique.
				* Modifie le pourcentage de saleté du véhicule qui sera nettoyé.

		## Multijoueur :
		* Vous devez avoir les droits d'administrateur pour accéder au menu des paramètres.
		* Vous pouvez utiliser les paramètres globaux pour toutes les fermes ou changer par ferme.

		Ce mod est fait par moi à partir de zéro.

		Si vous avez des problèmes avec le mod ou quoi que ce soit d'autre, s'il vous plaît contactez-moi sur :
		https://github.com/Bobster82/FS22_AutoRepair ]]>
		</fr>

		<nl>
		<![CDATA[ AutoRepair houdt uw voertuig in goede staat.

		+ Repareert uw voertuig automatisch wanneer het schade heeft.
		+ Overspuit uw voertuig automatisch wanneer het versleten is.
		+ Was uw voertuig automatisch wanneer het vuil is geworden.

		## Hoe te gebruiken:
		* Wanneer je deze mod in je fs22 mod map plaatst, staat standaard alleen automatisch repareren aan.
		* Druk op de linker Alt + r toets om het menu te openen.
				* Verander het tijdsinterval wanneer voertuigen/tools gecontroleerd moeten worden.
				* Activeer/deactiveer automatisch repareren.
				* Wijzig bij welk schade percentage een voertuig/gereedschap wordt gerepareerd.
				* Activeer/deactiveer automatisch overspuiten.
				* Wijzig bij welk slijtagepercentage een voertuig/gereedschap overgespoten wordt.
				* Activeer/deactiveer automatisch wassen.
				* Wijzig bij welk percentage vuil een voertuig gewassen wordt.

		## Multiplayer:
		* Je hebt admin rechten nodig om het menu te openen
		* Je kunt globale instellingen gebruiken voor alle boerderijen of per boerderij veranderen.

		Deze mod is gemaakt door mij vanaf nul.

		Als je problemen hebt met de mod of iets gerelateerd, neem dan contact met me op:
		https://github.com/Bobster82/FS22_AutoRepair ]]>
		</nl>

	</description>
	<version>2.0.0.5</version>
	<multiplayer supported="true"/>
	<iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>

	<actions>
		<action name="AR_openMenu" axisType="HALF" />
  	</actions>

  	<inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="AR_openMenu">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_r"/>
		</actionBinding>
  	</inputBinding>

  	<l10n filenamePrefix="Translations/translation"/>
	
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="AutoRepair.lua"/>
	</extraSourceFiles>	

</modDesc>
