<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="63">
    <author>Bobster82</author>
	<title>
		<en>AutoRepair</en>
		<it>Auto Riparazione</it>
    </title>
	<description>
		<en>
		<![CDATA[ AutoRepair keeps your vehicle healty.

		+ Repairs your vehicle automaticly when it has damage.
		+ Repaint your vehicle automaticly when it has worn out.
		+ Clean your vehicle automaticly when it got dirty.

		## How to use:
		* When you place this mod in your fs22 mods folder, only auto repair is on by default.
		* Press Left Alt + r key to acces the menu.
				* Change the time interval when vehicles/tools needs to be checked.
			    * Activate/deactivate auto repair.
				* Change at what damage percent a vehicle/tool get repaired.
				* Activate/deactivate auto repaint.
				* Change at what wear percent a vehicle/tool get repainted.
				* Activate/deactivate auto clean.
				* Change at what dirt percent a vehicle get cleaned.

		This mod is made by me from scratch.

		If you have any issues with the mod or anything related, please contact me on:
		https://github.com/Bobster82/FS22_AutoRepair ]]>
		</en>
		<it>
		<![CDATA[Auto Riparazione mantiene il tuo veicolo sano.

		+ Ripara automaticamente il tuo veicolo in caso di danni.
		+ Rivernicia automaticamente il tuo veicolo quando è usurato.
		+ Pulisci automaticamente il tuo veicolo quando si sporca.

		## Come usare:
		* Quando inserisci questa mod nella cartella mod fs22, solo la riparazione automatica è attiva per impostazione predefinita.
		* Premi il tasto Alt sinistro + R per accedere al menù.
		* Modificare l'intervallo di tempo in cui è necessario controllare veicoli/strumenti.
		* Attiva/disattiva la riparazione automatica.
		* Cambia la percentuale di danno che un veicolo/strumento viene riparato.
		* Attiva/disattiva la riverniciatura automatica.
		* Cambia la percentuale di usura che un veicolo/attrezzo viene riverniciato.
		* Attiva/disattiva la pulizia automatica.
		* Cambia la percentuale di sporco che un veicolo viene pulito.

		Questa mod è stata creata da me da zero.

		Se hai problemi con la mod o qualcosa di correlato, contattami su:
		https://github.com/Bobster82/FS22_AutoRepair ]]>
		</it>
	</description>
    <version>2.0.0.4</version>
	<multiplayer supported="true"/>
	<iconFilename>store.dds</iconFilename>

	<actions>
    	<action name="AR_openMenu" axisType="HALF" />
  	</actions>

  	<inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="AR_openMenu">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_r"/>
		</actionBinding>
  	</inputBinding>

  	<l10n>
		<text name="input_AR_openMenu">
			<en>AutoRepair: Open the settings menu</en>
			<it>Auto Riparazione: Apri il menù delle impostazioni</it>
		</text>
  	</l10n>
	
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="AutoRepair.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>	

</modDesc>
